are some men depressive because of
thyroid issues
uh great question Stephen there's no
question that's a a huge component um
there's more studies than I can count in
my head discussing and describing the
association and and practically the
causation of what would be major
depressive disorder related to
hypothyroidism or low thyroid um so I I
think hypothyroidism
I don't know it's funny in conventional
medicine you'll hear a lot of times oh
hypothyroidism it's so overtreated um
and they're probably in some ways
they're probably right I think they're
probably overtreated and inappropriately
treated at the same time uh most people
are just given right the Synthroid or
Leo thyroxine or synthetic T4 which
doesn't always uh pan out perfectly for
every single patient so again it's
always in my opinion best to use a
mixture of T3 and T4 um and and and we
see great results with that and so again
uh some patients coming in just because
they have low testosterone well if you
don't fix the low thyroid they might not
have a complete resolution of those
depression symptoms
[music]